Finding Aid for Jennifer Granholm papers, 1992-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Legal Division
  - Michelle Rick: Deputy Legal Counsel
    - Protect Agenda
      - Child Predators
        - House of Representatives Legislation 2005 (Box 77)
        - Michigan Child Registry 2004-2005 (Box 77)
        - National Registry 2005 (Box 77)
      - Consumer Advocate 2005 (Box 77)
      - Education Commission 2005 (Box 77)
      - General Information (from Carrie Lewand)
        - Issue Memos 2005, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 77)
          (includes a CD titled It’s as Easy as Buying a Book Online: Coverage of Alcohol Internet Purchase by Minor)
        - Governor -- Protection & Crime Reduction 2005 (Box 77)
      - Prescription Drugs
        - Board of Pharmacy Rules/PA 368-Pertinent Parts 2005 (Box 77)
        - Prescription Pricefinder Main File 2004-2005 (Box 77)
        - Other States 2004-2005 (Box 77)
        - Department of Community Health (DCH) 2005 (Box 77)
        - Cox Pricefinder 2005 (Box 77)
      - Protocol Issues 2007 (Box 77)
      - Sarbanes-Oxley
        - Non-Profit Panel Report/Non-Profit Corp. Act 2005 (Box 77)
        - Dox from Corina Peña Andorfer 2003 (Box 77)
      - Video Games
        - Legal Issues 2005 (Box 77)
        - Legislation 2005 (Box 78)
        - Part 1 2005 (Box 78)
        - Part 2 2005 (Box 78)
        - Bill Package 2005 (Box 78)
      - Public Acts -- Photo ID 2006 (Box 78)
      - Public Officials -- Flint City 2007 (Box 78)
      - Research -- Amicus Briefs 2005 (Box 78)
      - State Bar Association
        - Articles
          - Equal Employment Opportunity Case Law Update 2007 (Box 78)
          - The State Office of Administrative Hearings and Rules 2006 (Box 78)
        - Judicial Qualifications Interviews 2006-2007 (Box 78)
        - Seminar: Gasoline Pricing and Antitrust Laws 2006 (Box 78)
      - Transportation
        - Hafer Trucking 2007 (Box 78)
        - Wahby/State Transportation Commission 2006-2007 (Box 78)
      - Treasury -- Tobacco (Diligent Enforcement) 2003 (Box 78)
      - Entertainment Software Association (ESA) v. Granholm,et al 2005-2006, 5 folders (Box 78)
      - ESA v. Granholm, et. al., Appendix to Defendants’ Response to Plaintiffs’ Motion for a Preliminary Injunction, 5 folders (Box 78)
      - ESA v. Granholm, et. al., Appendix to Defendants’ Response to Plaintiffs’ Motion for a Preliminary Injunction, 4 folders (Box 79)
  - Brandon Hofmeister: Deputy Legal Counsel
    - Economic Development
      - 48C Qualifying Advanced Energy Project Credit 2009 (Box 79)
      - 3S Solar Energy undated (Box 79)
      - Acciona Windpower undated (Box 79)
      - Advanced Battery 2008 (Box 79)
      - Algae 2008 (Box 79)
      - Applied Materials 2008 (Box 79)
      - Alpena Prototype Biorefinery circa 2010 (Box 79)
      - Camaret 2007 (Box 79)
      - Centers of Excellence 2008 (Box 79)
      - Chicago Climate Exchange 2007 (Box 79)
      - Department of Energy: Wind Manufacturing Roadmap 2009 (Box 79)
      - DSIRE Tax Incentives 2007 (Box 79)
      - Evergreen (Solar) 2008 (Box 79)
      - Flint Biogas 2008 (Box 79)
      - Flint Project (water) 2008 (Box 79)
      - Four Winns 2008 (Box 79)
      - Funding 2007 (Box 79)
      - Franklin Energy Turbines 2007 (Box 79)
      - General Electric (GE) 2010 (Box 79)
      - Green Jobs 2008-2009 (Box 79)
      - Green Parking undated (Box 79)
      - Grid Logic 2009 (Box 79)
      - HelioVolt 2009 (Box 79)
      - Hemlock Semi-conductor 2008 (Box 79)
      - Job Studies 2009-2010 (Box 79)
      - Kalyani Group/Kenersys 2010 (Box 79)
      - L3 Communications 2009 (Box 79)
      - Liebher Group undated (Box 79)
      - MAG/Dowding 2008 (Box 79)
      - McKinsey & Company 2010 (Box 79)
      - Michigan Energy Future “Signatories” 2007 (Box 79)
      - NGA Workshop-Clean Energy-Seattle, WA 2008 (Box 79)
      - NextEnergy: Drivetrain Reliability Center 2009 (Box 79)
      - Public Private Partnerships (PPP) 2009 (Box 79)
      - Project Better Place 2008 (Box 79)
      - RES (Renewable Energy Systems company) 2007 (Box 79)
      - Renewafuel 2008 (Box 79)
      - Jobs Projections 2007-2010, 2 folders (Box 80)
      - SEP/CEAM 2007-2010 (Box 80)
      - Siemens
        - Clean Energy Center 2009 (Box 80)
        - Clean Gas Turbine Center 2009 (Box 80)
      - Suncrest Energy (Plasma Gratification) 2008 (Box 80)
      - Sunenergy 2010 (Box 80)
      - Tax Policy 2007-2008 (Box 80)
      - The Right Place/MEDC: Advancing West Michigan 2009 (Box 80)
      - TODA 2009 (Box 80)
      - Uni-Solar 2008 (Box 80)
      - University Collaborations 2007-2008 (Box 80)
      - Ventower Industries 2009 (Box 80)
      - Verde Partners undated (Box 80)
      - Verso Paper 2010 (Box 80)
      - Vortex Hydro 2007 (Box 80)
      - Wixom Project undated (Box 80)
    - Biofuels
      - 21st Century R&D 2007-2008 (Box 80)
      - Alpena Wood Plant 2008 (Box 80)
      - Low Carbon Fuel Standard 2007-2008 (Box 80)
      - Ethanol Prices 2007-2008 (Box 80)
      - U.P. Biomass 2009 (Box 80)
      - Ethanol 2006-2008 (Box 80)
    - Renewable Energy
      - Offshore Wind
        - General 2007-2010, 2 folders (Box 80)
        - Bottomlands 2005-2008 (Box 80)
        - Dry Run 2005, 2008 (Box 80)
        - Department of the Interior -- Mineral Management Service circa 2008 (Box 81)
        - Lakebed Alteration GIS undated (Box 81)
        - Michigan Great Lakes Wind Council Meetings and Working Groups 2009 (Box 81)
        - Wind Siting 2008 (Box 81)
        - Harnessing Wisconsin’s Resources 2008-2009 (Box 81)
      - Feed in Tariffs
        - General 2007-2010 (Box 81)
        - Research Doc’s for Ontario, Germany, Italy, and Spain 2007-2008 (Box 81)
      - Center for Climate Strategies (Greenhouse Gas Inventory & Reference Case Projections 1990-2025) 2008 (Box 81)
      - Detroit Eco-Village 2007 (Box 81)
      - Distributed Generation 2008 (Box 81)
      - Faith Community 2003, 2005 (Box 81)
      - Green Schools undated (Box 81)
      - Interconnection 2008-2009 (Box 81)
      - M.S.U. Cooperative Extension 2009 (Box 81)
      - NetMetering 2007-2010 (Box 81)
      - State Oil and Gas Reserves 2003, 2008 (Box 81)
      - Solar 2007-2008 (Box 81)
      - Roadmap
        - California Materials 2008 (Box 81)
        - Weekly Meetings 2008 (Box 81)
        - Roadmap Legislation undated (Box 81)
        - Drafts 2007-2008 (Box 81)
      - Water -- Water Cluster 2009 (Box 81)
      - Solar
        - Manufacturing. 2009 (Box 81)
        - Aspire 2009 (Box 81)
        - Cost Study 2009 (Box 81)
        - DOW Solar Shingle undated (Box 81)
        - State Government Projects 2009 (Box 81)
      - Transmission 2007-2010 (Box 82)
      - Wind
        - General 2007-2008 (Box 82)
        - 20% by 2030, 2008-2009 (Box 82)
        - Aggregated Demand 2009 (Box 82)
        - April 2007 Conference in East Lansing, 2007 (Box 82)
        - American Wind Energy Association (AWEA) Stats 2007 (Box 82)
        - Birds 2003-2008 (scattered) (Box 82)
        - Carleton College Turbine 2007 (Box 82)
        - CMS-PPA 2010 (Box 82)
        - CMS Wind Strategy undated (Box 82)
        - Commercial Forest Land Tax Break 2008 (Box 82)
        - Community Wind 2008 (Box 82)
        - Land Use Regulations 2005, 2008 (Box 82)
        - MEDC Pitch Materials 2008 (Box 82)
        - Northern Power undated (Box 82)
        - Iberdrola 2008 (Box 82)
        - West Michigan Projects 2008 (Box 82)
        - Financing Projects 2008 (Box 82)
        - Wyandotte 2008 (Box 82)
        - DTE Cost Projections 2008 (Box 82)
        - Wind Manufacturing 2009 (Box 82)
        - Resource Zone Board Filings 2009 (Box 82)
        - Thumb Projects 2007-2008 (Box 82)
      - Electricity
        - Renewable Portfolio Standard
          - Dormant Commerce Clause 2007-2008 (Box 82)
          - Amendments 2007-2008, 3 folders (Box 82)
          - Cost Trigger 2006-2008 (Box 83)
          - Patterson 2008 (Box 83)
          - Wholesale Contracts 2007 (Box 83)
          - Labor Provision 2007 (Box 83)
          - Meeting Notes 2007-2008 (Box 83)
          - Renewable Energy Certificates (RECs) 2005-2007 (Box 83)
          - Definition circa 2008 (Box 83)
          - Bills 2007-2008 (Box 83)
          - Workgroups 2007 (Box 83)
          - State 2005-2008 (Box 83)
          - Statutes 2005-2008, 3 folders (Box 83)
          - Public Service Commission (PSC) Temporary Order 2008 (Box 83)
          - Rulemaking 2009 (Box 83)
          - DeVos 2008 (Box 83)
          - Mackinac Center 2008 (Box 83)
          - Press 2008 (Box 83)
          - Market Reaction to Consumers Energy’s and Detroit Edison’s RFPs for Renewable Energy 2009 (Box 83)
        - ESMAP Technical Report -- Grid Assessment 2007 (Box 83)
        - Who Owns Renewable Energy Certificates? An Exploration of Policy Options and Practice 2006 (Box 83)
        - Standard & Poor’s Methodology for Imputing Debt for U.S. Utilities’ Power Purchase Agreements 2007 (Box 83)
        - ABATE Positions 2007 (Box 83)
      - Senate Republican Bills 2007-2008 (Box 83)
      - Cogeneration 2006 (Box 83)
      - Wave and Tidal 2007 (Box 83)
      - General 2007-2008 (Box 83)
      - Carbon Capture and Sequestration 2004-2008, 5 folders (Box 83)
      - Carbon Capture and Sequestration 2005-2008, 7 folders (Box 84)
    - Energy Efficiency
      - Advanced Metering 2008 (Box 84)
      - Building Codes 2008 (Box 84)
      - Building Codes: Federal Requirements 2009 (Box 84)
      - Carbon Footprints--Cities 2008 (Box 84)
      - Decoupling 2007-2009 (Box 84)
      - Department of Energy (DOE) Grant -- Retrofit Ramp Up 2009 (Box 84)
      - Economic Impact 2008 (Box 84)
      - Energy Reform: Building Owners and Managers Association (BOMA) 2008 (Box 84)
      - Green Buildings 2008 (Box 84)
      - McKinsey 2009 (Box 84)
      - Michigan Retro-Fit Ramp-Up Initiative circa 2009 (Box 84)
      - Michigan Saves 2009 (Box 84)
      - Municipal Utility 213 Fixes 2008 (Box 84)
      - Pay-As-You-Save (PAYS) Program 2005 (Box 84)
      - Performance Contracting 2008 (Box 84)
      - P.A. 295 2007-2008 (Box 84)
      - State Government 2005-2008 (Box 84)
    - Electric Vehicles
      - General 2009 (Box 84)
      - Advanced Research Projects Agency-Energy (ARPA-E) 2009 (Box 84)
      - Bosch 2009 (Box 84)
      - Chrysler Bankruptcy 2009 (Box 84)
      - GM Bankruptcy 2009 (Box 84)
      - Public Service Commission (PSC) Policy 2008 (Box 84)
      - Public Service Commission (PSC) Task Force circa 2010 (Box 84)
      - Battery Plant National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA’s) Environmental Assessments 2010 (Box 84)
      - State of Michigan Annual Energy Report FY 2008, 2009 (Box 84)
    - State of the State 2010 (Box 85)
    - Michigan Climate Action Council
      - Economic Review 2010 (Box 85)
      - Transportation and Land Use Sectors (TLU) circa 2005 (Box 85)
      - Budget: -- 2011, 2008-2009 (Box 85)
    - Public Service Commission (PSC) Authority
      - Choice Report 2010 (Box 85)
      - COAL: Lansing Coal Plant 2008 (Box 85)
      - Electricity: Prices 2006-2008 (Box 85)
      - Enabling Statute for Renewable Portfolio Standards: Arizona, Maine, Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York 2007-2008 (Box 85)
      - Forecasting undated (Box 85)
      - Granholm Tour 2007 (Box 85)
      - Institute of Public Utilities (IPU) Forum January 2008 (Box 85)
      - Low-Income and Energy Efficiency Fund (LIEEF) 2010 (Box 85)
      - Michigan's 21st Century Electric Energy Plan 2007 (Box 85)
      - Michigan Manufacturers Association (MMA) and Chamber of Commerce Letter 2010 (Box 85)
      - Municipal and Cooperative Reform Bills 2007 (Box 85)
      - Energy Optimization (E.O.) Report 2009 (Box 85)
      - Utility Reform/Choice Report 2007 (Box 85)
      - Renewables 2004-2008 (Box 85)
      - Legal Authority 2007-2008 (Box 85)
    - Subject Files
      - 21st Century Jobs Fund 2008 (Box 85)
      - 527s Disclosure 2005 (Box 85)
      - Airport Zoning Act undated (Box 85)
      - Ann Arbor Film Festival 2006-2007 (Box 85)
      - Article: “All Lawyers are Public Interest Lawyers,” 2006 (Box 85)
      - Asbestos Reform 2006 (Box 85)
      - BAMN (Coalition to Defend Affirmative Action) v. Granholm 2007 (Box 85)
      - Bar Journal Article, Public Service 2003-2005 (Box 85)
      - Bay City Groundbreaking/Provisions/MDEQ/DLEG 2008 (Box 85)
      - Bidding Preferences 2005-2006 (Box 85)
      - Brownfields 2008 (Box 85)
      - Budget
        - Legislation 2003-2005 (Box 86)
        - Informal Attorney General Advice 2003-2007 (Box 86)
        - Crisis 2007 (Box 86)
      - Bullying 2005-2006, 2 folders (Box 86)
      - Cabinet Membership 2005-2006 (Box 86)
      - Camera Phones 2004 (Box 86)
      - Campaign Finance Reform 2005 (Box 86)
      - Capitol Committee--Ten Commandments 2005-2006 (Box 86)
      - Carbon Capture and Storage 2009, 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Car Subsidies 2005-2006 (Box 87)
      - Center for Michigan Articles 2006 (Box 87)
      - Child Abuse Database 2004 (Box 87)
      - Child Protection/Legislation 2005 (Box 87)
      - Child Support 2006 (Box 87)
      - Child Safety 2005 (Box 87)
      - Children -- Internet Safety 2005 (Box 87)
      - China 2006 (Box 87)
      - Climate Action Council 2007 (Box 87)
      - Climate Change: McKinsey Study 2007 (Box 87)
      - Clinton Accomplishments 2005 (Box 87)
      - Code Adam 2005-2006 (Box 87)
      - College Loans 2007 (Box 87)
      - Community Colleges, 4 Year Degrees 2007 (Box 87)
      - Conflicts of Interest 2006 (Box 87)
      - Consumer Protection 2005-2006 (Box 87)
      - Cool Cities 2006 (Box 87)
      - Corporate Governance 2005 (Box 87)
      - Correspondence 2006 (Box 87)
      - Cox -- Taxpayer Amicus 2006 (Box 87)
      - Crime 2004-2005 (Box 87)
      - Crime in Detroit/The Joshua Project 2006 (Box 87)
      - Delphi 2005-2007 (Box 87)
      - Detroit Light Rail 2008 (Box 87)
      - Detroit Medical Center/Wayne State University
        - 11/22 Memorandum of Understanding, 2006 (Box 88)
        - 2006 Agreement (Box 88)
        - Accreditation council for Graduate Medical Education (ACGME) 2003-2007, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - Agreement Original 2006 (Box 88)
        - Agreement Summary 2006-2007 (Box 88)
        - Anti-Kickback Statute 2008 (Box 88)
        - Charity Care 2007-2008, 2 folders (Box 88)
        - Correspondence 2006 (Box 88)
        - David Fink’s Proposed Final Contracts 2007 (Box 88)
        - Dispute, Alleged “Overpayments,” 2008 (Box 88)
        - DMC Materials 2007-2008 (Box 88)
        - Fund for Medical Research Corporate Documents 2004-2005 (Box 88)
        - Joe Schwartz, Blue Ribbon Commission Report 2007 (Box 88)
        - Meeting Notes 2008 (Box 88)
        - Michigan State University (MSU) Materials 2007 (Box 88)
        - Michigan State University (MSU) Program 2007 (Box 88)
        - News Articles 2006-2007 (Box 88)
        - Negotiation Materials 2006 (Box 88)
        - Notes -- Clinical 2006-2007 (Box 88)
        - Notes and Materials -- Teaching 2007 (Box 88)
        - Old K Negotiations 2006 (Box 88)
        - “Organizing for Economic Development: Lessons from Leading Life Sciences Regions,” 2007 (Box 88)
        - Parking 2004-2008 (Box 88)
        - Previous Contracts 2003-2004 (Box 88)
        - Slot Requirements 2006 (Box 88)
        - Stark Law 2008 (Box 88)
        - University Physician Group (UPG) Corporate Documents 2008 (Box 88)
        - Wayne State University School of Medicine Strategic Plan and Other Materials 2007 (Box 88)
      - Detroit Water and Sewer 2006 (Box 88)
      - DNA Collection 2005 (Box 88)
      - Domestic Partner Benefits 2008 (Box 88)
      - Domestic Violence 2004-2005 (Box 88)
      - Duderstadt Roadmap 2005 (Box 88)
      - Economy 2006 (Box 88)
      - Elder Abuse 2005 (Box 88)
      - Emergency Management FERMI 2 Exercise 2006 (Box 88)
      - Emergency Management -- General 2007 (Box 88)
      - Energy Costs/Articles 2005 (Box 88)
      - Energy Policy 2006 (Box 88)
      - Executive Directives and Orders
        - Executive Directive, 21st Century Energy Plan 2006 (Box 88)
        - Executive Order: Macomb County Commission on Higher Education and Economic Growth 2005-2006 (Box 88)
        - Executive Reorganization Orders (EROs) 2007 (Box 88)
        - Executive Order 2006-5 2004-2005 (Box 88)
        - Executive Order 2007-4 2007 (Box 88)
        - Executive Order 2008-1, Employee Misclassification 2004, 2007-2008 (Box 89)
        - Executive Order 2008-2, Insurance Advocate 2007-2008 (Box 89)
      - Executive Privilege 2005-2008 (Box 89)
      - Executive Reorganization Authority 2005 (Box 89)
      - F.D.A. Immunity 2006 (Box 89)
      - Federal Policy
        - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act (ARRA) Energy 2009 (Box 89)
        - Autos 2010 (Box 89)
        - Cap and Trade 2008-2009 (Box 89)
        - Carbon Markets 2008 (Box 89)
        - Carbon Tax 2008 (Box 89)
        - Carbon Trust 2009 (Box 89)
        - Climate Change (Gov. Accountability Office) 2008 (Box 89)
        - Climate Change: National Security 2009 (Box 89)
        - Climate Impacts 2009 (Box 89)
        - Climate Policy: Michigan Companies Affected 2009 (Box 89)
        - Copenhagen Accord 2009 (Box 89)
        - Council on Competitiveness Report 2009 (Box 89)
        - Department of Energy
          - Budget 2010 (Box 89)
          - Funding Report -- Rare Isotope Beams 2010 (Box 89)
          - Loan Guarantees 2007-2010 (Box 89)
          - Oak Ridge National Lab/Michigan Office 2010 (Box 89)
        - Dingell Draft 2008 (Box 89)
          (Carbon Caps Trade Bill)
        - DOW Chemical 2008 (Box 89)
        - Energy Information Administration (EIA) Stats 2008 (Box 89)
        - Electrification Coalition Legislation Before Congress 2010 (Box 89)
        - Energy Efficiency and Conservation Block Grants (EECBG) 2010 (Box 89)
        - EPA Endangerment undated (Box 89)
        - Farm Bill 2008 (Box 89)
        - Federal Energy Bill 2007 (Box 89)
        - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) 2009 (Box 89)
        - Federal Grants 2008 (Box 89)
        - Federal Production Tax Credit 2008 (Box 89)
        - Federal Renewable Energy Standard (R.E.S.) undated (Box 89)
        - Index of Law Reviews on Cap & Trade in Carbon Dioxide Emission 2007-2008 (Box 89)
        - Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change (IPCC) Report 2007 (Box 90)
        - International Climate Stats 2009 (Box 90)
        - Kerry/Graham 2009 (Box 90)
        - Lieberman-Warner Climate Security Act 2008 (Box 90)
        - McCain/Lexington Project 2008 (Box 90)
        - M.G.A. Climate Accord 2007 (Box 90)
          (Midwestern Greenhouse Gas Reduction Accord)
        - M.G.A. Recos 2009 (Box 90)
          (MGA Energy Security and Climate Stewardship Roadmap: Building a New Energy Economy)
        - Midwest Governors Association Compact 2007-2008 (Box 90)
        - National Governors Association 2007-2008 (Box 90)
        - NetMetering: PURPA Standard 2008 (Box 90)
        - Obama Plan 2008 (Box 90)
        - Qualified Energy Conservation Bonds 2008-2009 (Box 90)
        - Smart Grid Reports undated (Box 90)
        - U. S. Chamber 2008-2009 (Box 90)
        - Weatherization Production Trajectory (WAP) 2010 (Box 90)
        - Waxman Markey Cost Studies 2009-2010 (Box 90)
      - Flag Lowering 2006 (Box 90)
      - FOIA -- Sex Offenders 2006 (Box 90)
      - Gangs 1998-2001 (Box 90)
      - Government Reform 2007 (Box 90)
      - Hate Crimes 2007 (Box 90)
      - Headlee Amendment 2005 (Box 90)
      - Health Savings Accounts 2002-2006 (Box 90)
      - Heating Oil/Articles 2005 (Box 90)
      - Hemlock Semiconductor 2004-2008 (Box 90)
      - HIPAA, Privacy 2006 (Box 90)
      - Homeland Security
        - FEMA Certificates 2007 (Box 90)
        - Review -- Catastrophic Events 2006 (Box 90)
      - Humbug Marsh 2004-2006 (Box 90)
      - Identity Theft
        - Administrative Rule 2005 (Box 90)
        - Bill Analysis 2004-2006 (Box 90)
          (HB 5832 5833, 5834, 5835 5836)
        - Credit Freeze 2005 (Box 90)
        - General 2004-2006, 2 folders (Box 90)
        - News, Information, and Miscellaneous 2005 (Box 91)
        - Notification 2005-2006 (Box 91)
        - Notification in Other States 2005-2006 (Box 91)
        - Penalty 2005 (Box 91)
        - Security Freeze 2007 (Box 91)
      - Illegal Immigration 2007 (Box 91)
      - Immigration 2006 (Box 91)
      - Incompatible Offices 2006 (Box 91)
      - Individual Development Accounts 2005 (Box 91)
      - Interstate Compacts 2005 (Box 91)
      - Insurance Rates 2005 (Box 91)
      - Internet 2003-2006 (Box 91)
      - Iraqi Refugees 2007 (Box 91)
      - Item Pricing 2006 (Box 91)
      - Kennecott Mine 2007 (Box 91)
      - Lead 2006 (Box 91)
      - Legislative Vetoes 2006 (Box 91)
      - Lending State Credit 2005 (Box 91)
      - Local Government Fiscal 2006-2007 (Box 91)
      - Luntz Memo 2006 (Box 91)
      - Mackinac Bridge Re-Organization 2005 (Box 91)
      - Mackinac Speech 2007-2008 (Box 91)
      - Manufacturing Policy 2005 (Box 91)
      - Mental Health Courts 2003-2008, 2 folders (Box 91)
      - Mercury 2005 (Box 92)
      - Methamphetamine 2003-2005 (Box 92)
      - Michigan at the Millennium undated (Box 92)
      - Michigan Business Tax undated (Box 92)
      - Michigan Civil Rights Initiative 2006 (Box 92)
      - Michigan National Guard Counter Drug Plan 2005-2006 (Box 92)
      - Michigan Safe Schools 2004-2005 (Box 92)
      - Michigan Telecom Law 2006 (Box 92)
      - Mortgage Fraud 2006 (Box 92)
      - News Articles of Note 2006 (Box 92)
      - No Child Left Behind 2007 (Box 92)
      - Nuclear Power Plants 2005-2006 (Box 92)
      - Oakland Hills US Open bid Letter and Return Letter to Rick Bayliss 2007-2008 (Box 92)
      - Parental Notification 2006 (Box 92)
      - Parents Advisory Council 2005 (Box 92)
      - Patient Bill of Rights 2004 (Box 92)
      - Payday Loans 2005 (Box 92)
      - Predatory Lending 2007 (Box 92)
      - Prescription Drug Prices 2005 (Box 92)
      - Prevailing Wage 2007 (Box 92)
      - Prima Civitas 2007 (Box 92)
      - Procurement Policy 2004-2007 (Box 92)
      - Project Labor Agreements 2003, 2006 (Box 92)
      - Promise Zones 2007 (Box 92)
      - Proposal 2, University Reform 2006-2007 (Box 93)
      - Public Corruption 2005-2006 (Box 93)
      - Racial Justice 2006 (Box 93)
      - Redistricting 2005 (Box 93)
      - Removal of Local Officials 2008 (Box 93)
      - Renewable Energy
        - Biofuels
          - Engine Efficiency 2007 (Box 93)
          - Underwriters Laboratory 2007 (Box 93)
        - Utilities
          - HB ’s 5520-5524, 2007-2008 (Box 93)
          - HB 5524 Conference 2007-2008 (Box 93)
          - Representative Nofs Substitute Bill 2008 (Box 93)
          - Representative Nofs’ Substitute Suggested Amendments 2008 (Box 93)
      - Safe Schools 2005-2006, 2 folders (Box 93)
      - Same Sex Benefits 2006 (Box 93)
      - School Finance 2006 (Box 93)
      - Sentencing Guidelines Reform 2007 (Box 93)
      - Sex Offender Registry 2005-2006 (Box 93)
      - Shelly Bean--Accident Scene Legislation 2005-2006 (Box 93)
      - Single Gender Schools 2006 (Box 93)
      - Smoking & Local Governments 2005 (Box 93)
      - Sovereign Moor 2006 (Box 93)
      - Spam 2005 (Box 93)
      - Spyware 2005-2006 (Box 93)
      - State of the State 2006 (Box 93)
      - State Treasurer 2004, 2006 (Box 93)
      - Statutes Retained 2007 (Box 93)
      - Statutes Transferred 2007 (Box 93)
      - Sue Sarin Issue 2006-2007 (Box 94)
      - Supreme Court 2006-2007 (Box 94)
      - Tax Policy 2006 (Box 94)
      - Teacher Tenure Commission 2005, 2007 (Box 94)
      - Teen Drinking and Driving 2005 (Box 94)
      - Tort Law Revision, Michigan Supreme Court undated (Box 94)
      - Toyota